Let's take our Choo Choo Shimmy and add a twist to it literally.
So we're going to first start with our feet up on Relevee, since we've already tried that hopefully.
And we're going to lift our hips up in toward our rib cage.
Watch your upper body.
Make sure that belly button's pulled in nice and tight.
So we're going to bring it, the right hip forward, and then bring it back.
Good.
Right hip forward, bring the left hip forward, and back, and forward, and back.
Little faster.
Forward, forward, forward, forward, forward.
And again, speed it up.
Make sure your upper body stays nice and level.
Keep those ankles pulled in toward each other.
Keep your hands from moving around.
Keep your head nice and still.
Very good.
Keep that belly button in.
And then when you practice this, try it different tempos.
Practice it in the mirror so that you make sure your posture stays nice and pretty.